<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Telegram Style</title>
    <description>A magazine of style and substance.
</description>
    <link>http://telegram-creative.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://telegram-creative.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 08:43:35 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 08:43:35 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Craft of Small Business</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There was great article in the New Yorker recently about the craft of small businesses:
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.newyorker.com/business/currency/small-bountiful-small-business-craft-beer&quot;&gt;http://www.newyorker.com/business/currency/small-bountiful-small-business-craft-beer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[S]mall breweries came back. Their beers were not better advertised and certainly not better priced. Rather, the crafts went after an enormous blind spot for the big breweries—namely, flavor. I don’t entirely mean to be snide; more precisely, craft beer succeeded by opting not to compete directly, instead pursuing what can be called a “true differentiation” strategy. That means they established a product that, in the mind of the consumer, is markedly and undeniably different (as opposed to “false differentiation,” which is more or less the same thing with different packaging). True differentiation, if it works, actually changes consumer preferences. The dedicated craft-beer drinker, once he’s hooked, no longer cares if Coors Light costs three dollars less.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href=&quot;http://telegram-co.com/&quot;&gt;Telegram Jeans&lt;/a&gt; are getting off the ground, we&amp;#39;d like to think that we&amp;#39;re differentiated in the fact that we&amp;#39;re small. We&amp;#39;re not some big manufacturer or corporate conglomerate. We&amp;#39;re just a few people who care intensely about the product we put out. We care enough about the product that every pair of jeans we put out is handmade, whether you call it &amp;quot;craft&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;small batch&amp;quot; or whatever buzzword you want.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 08:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2015/02/12/the-craft-of-small-business.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2015/02/12/the-craft-of-small-business.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rock Music and Skinny Jeans</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A good pair of jeans is hard to find, because for all the companies that make them, very few put in the legwork for both a very good fit and very fine materials. There are many &amp;quot;expensive&amp;quot; pairs, but there are fewer truly well-made pairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For &lt;a href=&quot;http://telegram-co.com/&quot;&gt;Telegram&lt;/a&gt; we&amp;#39;re only doing one cut to start, and that&amp;#39;s a skinny cut made of Japanese denim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Skinny jeans have been a part the &amp;quot;leading edge&amp;quot; of culture for decades now, and it&amp;#39;s remarkable how well this look has held up. (Especially when paired with a &lt;a href=&quot;http://telegramstyle.com/2015/02/02/the-appeal-of-the-beaten-up-leather-jacket.html&quot;&gt;nice leather jacket&lt;/a&gt; and bedhead-style hair). Let&amp;#39;s recap:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Older: &lt;a href=&quot;https://godsofadvertising.files.wordpress.com/2013/07/ramones.jpg&quot;&gt;The Ramones&lt;/a&gt;, or the &lt;a href=&quot;https://tallglassofstyle.files.wordpress.com/2013/05/sex-pistols.jpg&quot;&gt;Sex Pistols&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Newer: &lt;a href=&quot;http://images4.fanpop.com/image/photos/19300000/NME-interview-the-strokes-19375742-2050-2560.jpg&quot;&gt;The Strokes&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;http://i.guim.co.uk/static/w-620/h--/q-95/sys-images/Music/Pix/pictures/2012/1/13/1326453926057/Justice-006.jpg&quot;&gt;Justice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even newer: &lt;a href=&quot;http://fashionbomb.thefashionbomb.netdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/Lenny-Kravitzs-Super-Bowl-XLIX-Halftime-Performance-Saint-Laurent-Fringed-Black-Leather-Motorcycle-Jacket-Destroyed-Jeans-and-Tan-Suede-Boots-and-Natalia-Fedner-Gold-Chain-Shirt.jpg&quot;&gt;Lenny Kravitz at the Super Bowl&lt;/a&gt;, or Kanye&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.therooster.ca/wp-content/uploads/kanye-%20fashion-%20street%20style-%20candid%20photo-%20winter%20fall%20style-%20casual.jpg&quot;&gt;more recent looks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why skinny jeans? Everyone has their own tastes, and natural variation in body proportions mean that cuts from some manufacturers look great on some but hideous on others. But for those of reasonably slim build, a narrow cut fits the bill just right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing we found when designing and cutting our own jeans was that a lot of companies get it wrong. They either make the jean out of very rigid denim (which is too hard to move around in) or very elastic denim (which doesn&amp;#39;t wear as well as pure cotton). For Telegram we looked for a happy medium between these two -- we found an importer who could hook us up with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kaihara-denim.com/english/company/history.html&quot;&gt;Kaihara denim&lt;/a&gt;, from a mill dating back to 1893 (!). We then designed, cut, and sewed our first pairs here in Brooklyn, and found that the result was form-fitting but durable, and comfortable to boot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, these are handmade, &amp;quot;artisinal&amp;quot; quality jeans, so the price went up commeasurately. But we think it&amp;#39;s worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The materials and workmanship speak for themselves, and our product photos show them off beautifully. Check it out: &lt;a href=&quot;http://telegram-co.com/products/telegram-jeans&quot;&gt;Telegram Jeans&lt;/a&gt;. Japanese denim, cut and sewn in Brooklyn.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2015 11:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2015/02/08/rock-music-and-skinny-jeans.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2015/02/08/rock-music-and-skinny-jeans.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Build One to Throw Away</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In engineering there&amp;#39;s a saying, &amp;quot;build one to throw away&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You make a prototype and then scrap it. You try out ideas in the hope that one of them sticks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because the real metric of progress isn&amp;#39;t how much you&amp;#39;ve made, it&amp;#39;s how much you&amp;#39;ve thrown away.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 09:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2015/02/04/build-one-to-throw-away.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2015/02/04/build-one-to-throw-away.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Music Tuesday: FKA Twigs and Run the Jewels</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been going through Picthfork&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;http://pitchfork.com/features/staff-lists/9558-the-50-best-albums-of-2014/5/&quot;&gt;Best of 2014&lt;/a&gt; and I&amp;#39;ve got to say, the top two picks are really spot-on. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=USTTGsNrTmk&quot;&gt;Run the Jewels 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3yDP9MKVhZc&quot;&gt;FKA Twigs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a broader sense though, it seems like music reviews are on the decline. Not just because of fewer readers for traditional publications (Rolling Stone, etc.) but also the rise of recommendation engines. When anyone can look up a Spotify playlist or have Pandora make music for you, what&amp;#39;s lost?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Especially since not &amp;quot;picking&amp;quot; or reading about or being invested in your own music results in a loss of agency -- if you&amp;#39;re not picking the music yourself, you have less at stake, and maybe you care a bit less about what&amp;#39;s happening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These two records are both in a dark, moody, atmospheric vein, and they both have killer style. Graffiti and soul:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/article_images/2015-02-03/run-the-jewels-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the future&amp;#39;s getting darker and grittier, we&amp;#39;ll all need darker clothes to catch up. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 08:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2015/02/03/music-tuesday-fka-twigs-and-run-the-jewels.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2015/02/03/music-tuesday-fka-twigs-and-run-the-jewels.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Appeal of the Beaten-up Leather Jacket</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Most guys have a beaten-up leather jacket in the closet (I&amp;#39;ve got several), and the best thing about them is that the way they&amp;#39;re weathered matches the lifestyle so exactly. There are a few fabrics -- leather and denim mostly -- that conform to your body better the longer  you wear them, and that look better with age than out of the box. A few of our favorites:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/article_images/2015-02-02/scott-perfecto.jpg&quot;&gt;Schott&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/article_images/2015-02-02/julius-leather.jpg&quot;&gt;Julius&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/article_images/2015-02-02/dior-homme-4-pocket.jpg&quot;&gt;Dior Homme 4-Pocket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/article_images/2015-02-02/rick-owens-stooges.jpg&quot;&gt;Rick Owens Stooges&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, all of these are hideously expensive. But isn&amp;#39;t that what nice things are about? Whenever I waffle about the price of clothing, I think of this quote by Yohji Yamamoto:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I make clothing like armor. My clothing protects you from unwelcome eyes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; is what good clothing is about.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 08:49:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2015/02/02/the-appeal-of-the-beaten-up-leather-jacket.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2015/02/02/the-appeal-of-the-beaten-up-leather-jacket.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Before Launch</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;At &lt;a href=&quot;http://telegram-co.com/&quot;&gt;Telegram Co.&lt;/a&gt; we&amp;#39;re gearing up for launch. Our product is simple, but even the simplest things go to hell when you&amp;#39;re not looking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being prepared takes time and effort. A restaurant will soft open, a website may be invite-only, a product may sell out its first run (if you&amp;#39;re lucky) or just sit on the shelves (if you&amp;#39;re not).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are you prepared for?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepared in business. Prepared for that meeting, or that client pitch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepared in art. Prepared to get on stage, to play music or talk or hang your paintings in a gallery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepared to put yourself out there. To show your product to the world and see who bites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was reading an interview with Shayne Oliver the other day, and one thing stuck out at me:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;It was more of a concept at first,&amp;quot; Shayne Oliver says of his outrageously inventive clothing line Hood By Air, which began in 2006 with a set of droll graphic t-shirts. &amp;quot;The tees would say ‘HOOD.&amp;#39; They were something we&amp;#39;d rock around town, almost to be obnoxious. We&amp;#39;d be running around wearing heels with parts down the middle of our hair, but wearing these t-shirts that said ‘Hood,&amp;#39; just to mix it up. I&amp;#39;d sometimes get into altercations with people over [the shirts], but at least I knew there was power in something I made.&amp;quot; (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.interviewmagazine.com/fashion/hood-by-air-shayne-oliver/&quot;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The power is in doing something remarkable. In making people stand up and take notice. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;re making our mark with Japanese denim jeans, cut and sewn in Brooklyn. Maybe you&amp;#39;d like to &lt;a href=&quot;http://telegram-co.com/pages/newsletter&quot;&gt;join us&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 13:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2015/02/01/before-launch.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2015/02/01/before-launch.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Every Day</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What do you do every day? Do you write, or make music, or practice a thing you&amp;#39;re good at? Do you look for new things, do you approach tasks with focus, do you feel inspired by your work?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or do you feel apathetic or tired, or &amp;quot;busy&amp;quot; all the time?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Busy-ness is the worst sin you can commit because it prevents you from doing the things you love. Students are &amp;quot;busy&amp;quot;, professionals are &amp;quot;busy&amp;quot;, and we&amp;#39;ll all be &amp;quot;busy&amp;quot; until we die. But it&amp;#39;s the things you fit in between the busy-ness that counts. The things you do daily, because otherwise they&amp;#39;ll never happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like this short post by &lt;a href=&quot;http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2014/12/daily.html&quot;&gt;Seth Godin&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s a fundamental difference between the things you do every day, every single day, and the things you do only when the spirit moves you.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
One difference is that once you&amp;#39;ve committed to doing something daily, you find that the spirit moves you, daily.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Rather than having a daily debate about today&amp;#39;s agenda, you can decide once that you will do something, and then decide every single day how to do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, I&amp;#39;m working full-time at a day job while starting a clothing company on the side (making &lt;a href=&quot;http://telegram-co.com/&quot;&gt;Japanese denim skinny jeans&lt;/a&gt; here in Brooklyn). And yet, I&amp;#39;m trying not to make too many commitments other than the ones I absolutely have to. Saying &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; to everything means you&amp;#39;re over-committed and under-enthused, which never ends well.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/27/every-day.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/27/every-day.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Make It?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Does what you&amp;#39;re making already exist?&lt;br&gt;
Why make music when there&amp;#39;s already so much music?&lt;br&gt;
Does the world really need another jeans company?&lt;br&gt;
If what you&amp;#39;re making already exists in the world, why make it at all? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But there&amp;#39;s a succinct answer: because nobody has done it quite right yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, I was into denim.&lt;br&gt;
I wanted a jean that was skinny enough to shock but not to bewilder.&lt;br&gt;
I wanted a jean that was well-made, but not overly stiff.&lt;br&gt;
I wanted a jean that represented a piece of New York, not anywhere else.&lt;br&gt;
I wanted a jean that fit well but wouldn&amp;#39;t.... &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I made it. &lt;a href=&quot;http://telegram-co.com/&quot;&gt;Japanese denim skinny jeans&lt;/a&gt;, cut and sewn in Brooklyn. Check it out!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2015 21:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/12/why-make-it.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/12/why-make-it.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Badlands</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is an excerpt from the Wikipedia article on &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Badlands_(film)&quot;&gt;Badlands&lt;/a&gt;, the 1973 film by Terrence Malick:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Malick, a protégé of Arthur Penn (whom he thanked in the film&amp;#39;s end credits), began work on Badlands after his second year as a student at the American Film Institute. In 1970, Malick, at age 27, began working on the screenplay during a road trip. &amp;#39;I wrote and, at the same time, developed a kind of sales kit with slides and video tape of actors, all with a view to presenting investors with something that would look ready to shoot,&amp;#39; Malick said. &amp;#39;To my surprise, they didn&amp;#39;t pay too much attention to it; they invested on faith. I raised about half the money and executive producer Edward Pressman the other half.&amp;#39; Malick paid $25,000 of his own funds. The remainder of his share was raised from professionals such as doctors and dentists. Badlands was the first feature film that Malick had written for himself to direct.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this a story on faith, or credibility? Malick was, at the time, an unknown director with an unproven product. All he had was a sales kit and a dream, but in a certain sense that&amp;#39;s all that matters: he had enough to convince investors that he was ready to take the next step, and they invested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS if you haven&amp;#39;t seen the movie before, it&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/B000NZY6S4/?tag=telegramco-20&quot;&gt;quite good&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2015 21:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/12/badlands.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/12/badlands.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Creating and Consuming</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote class=&quot;instagram-media&quot; data-instgrm-version=&quot;4&quot; style=&quot; background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);&quot;&gt;&lt;div style=&quot;padding:8px;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:#F8F8F8; line-height:0; margin-top:40px; padding:50% 0; text-align:center; width:100%;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:url(data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAACwAAAAsCAMAAAApWqozAAAAGFBMVEUiIiI9PT0eHh4gIB4hIBkcHBwcHBwcHBydr+JQAAAACHRSTlMABA4YHyQsM5jtaMwAAADfSURBVDjL7ZVBEgMhCAQBAf//42xcNbpAqakcM0ftUmFAAIBE81IqBJdS3lS6zs3bIpB9WED3YYXFPmHRfT8sgyrCP1x8uEUxLMzNWElFOYCV6mHWWwMzdPEKHlhLw7NWJqkHc4uIZphavDzA2JPzUDsBZziNae2S6owH8xPmX8G7zzgKEOPUoYHvGz1TBCxMkd3kwNVbU0gKHkx+iZILf77IofhrY1nYFnB/lQPb79drWOyJVa/DAvg9B/rLB4cC+Nqgdz/TvBbBnr6GBReqn/nRmDgaQEej7WhonozjF+Y2I/fZou/qAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC); display:block; height:44px; margin:0 auto -44px; position:relative; top:-22px; width:44px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p style=&quot; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/p/xsUPb0tLcl/&quot; style=&quot; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;&quot; target=&quot;_top&quot;&gt;A photo posted by Telegram (@telegram_co)&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;time style=&quot; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;&quot; datetime=&quot;2015-01-10T23:48:47+00:00&quot;&gt;Jan 10, 2015 at 3:48pm PST&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;script async defer src=&quot;//platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
This sticker lives on my laptop permanently. I can&amp;#39;t open my Macbook without seeing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn&amp;#39;t stand out much but it&amp;#39;s an important reminder. Laptops are for creating things, not consuming them. (If you want to read a book, or watch Netflix, or catch up on the day&amp;#39;s news, well, that&amp;#39;s what tablets and newspapers and television are for).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#39;Creating&amp;#39; doesn&amp;#39;t have to be entrepreneurial, or even artistic. It&amp;#39;s anything that brings new things into the world, or improves the things that are there. Writing code, editing photographs, finding recipes to cook or learning how to shine your shoes via YouTube. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me it&amp;#39;s a reminder to work on Telegram Co.—both this blog and the &amp;#39;product&amp;#39; side of it. (We&amp;#39;re making &lt;a href=&quot;http://telegram-co.com/&quot;&gt;Japanese denim jeans&lt;/a&gt; in Brooklyn, NY).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it doesn&amp;#39;t have to be entrepreneurial, or even artistic. Writing code, editing photographs, finding recipes to cook or learning how to shine your shoes via YouTube all count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sticker is a reminder to create things every day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 19:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/10/creating-and-consuming.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/10/creating-and-consuming.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
