<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Telegram Creative</title>
    <description>A blog about creating things.
</description>
    <link>http://telegram-creative.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://telegram-creative.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 16:58:04 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 16:58:04 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>On Writing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If I were to be brutally honest I wouldn&amp;#39;t be writing in the first place. Writing is a hard task: you put down words on paper, and others will read it (if you&amp;#39;re lucky).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reading involves an element of judgment: you agree or disagree with the author, or her style, and you decide on-the-spot whether to keep reading or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the same with making music, or art, or (to the more practical-minded) physical products like clothes or iPhones. You want to create a new thing and it&amp;#39;s difficult, and you&amp;#39;ll catch flak along the way from all angles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the most part it comes as doubt, not judgment. Not &amp;quot;that will never work&amp;quot;, but &amp;quot;Do you think that will work? Aren&amp;#39;t you worried?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Writing is hard. And music is hard, and art is hard, and making products people care about is hard. But we do it anyway. Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because it&amp;#39;s the only work worth doing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2014/12/28/on-writing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2014/12/28/on-writing.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wabi-sabi</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a book I read recently on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0981484603/?tag=telegramco-20&quot;&gt;Wabi-sabi&lt;/a&gt;. It reflects in itself the philosophy of wabi-sabi: soft cardboard cover, beautifully starched (but imperfect) pages, and a rough-cut edge to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wabi-sabi is the opposite of modernist design. Apple would never allow this kind of imperfection. But it&amp;#39;s a different kind of perfect: the perfect of your grandfather&amp;#39;s pocket-knife, or a motorcycle jacket that&amp;#39;s been ridden across the US and back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The perfect that comes from wear. From the kinds of things that get better with time, and not worse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An iPhone from three years ago is an old iPhone. A motorcycle jacket from three years ago is just getting started.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 16:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2014/12/21/wabi-sabi.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2014/12/21/wabi-sabi.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
