<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Telegram Creative</title>
    <description>A blog about creating things.
</description>
    <link>http://telegram-creative.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://telegram-creative.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2015 21:22:44 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2015 21:22:44 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Badlands</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is an excerpt from the Wikipedia article on &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Badlands_(film)&quot;&gt;Badlands&lt;/a&gt;, the 1973 film by Terrence Malick:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Malick, a protégé of Arthur Penn (whom he thanked in the film&amp;#39;s end credits), began work on Badlands after his second year as a student at the American Film Institute. In 1970, Malick, at age 27, began working on the screenplay during a road trip. &amp;#39;I wrote and, at the same time, developed a kind of sales kit with slides and video tape of actors, all with a view to presenting investors with something that would look ready to shoot,&amp;#39; Malick said. &amp;#39;To my surprise, they didn&amp;#39;t pay too much attention to it; they invested on faith. I raised about half the money and executive producer Edward Pressman the other half.&amp;#39; Malick paid $25,000 of his own funds. The remainder of his share was raised from professionals such as doctors and dentists. Badlands was the first feature film that Malick had written for himself to direct.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this a story on faith, or credibility? Malick was, at the time, an unknown director with an unproven product. All he had was a sales kit and a dream, but in a certain sense that&amp;#39;s all that matters: he had enough to convince investors that he was ready to take the next step, and they invested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS if you haven&amp;#39;t seen the movie before, it&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/B000NZY6S4/?tag=telegramco-20&quot;&gt;quite good&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2015 21:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/12/badlands.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/12/badlands.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Creating and Consuming</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote class=&quot;instagram-media&quot; data-instgrm-version=&quot;4&quot; style=&quot; background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);&quot;&gt;&lt;div style=&quot;padding:8px;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:#F8F8F8; line-height:0; margin-top:40px; padding:50% 0; text-align:center; width:100%;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:url(data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAACwAAAAsCAMAAAApWqozAAAAGFBMVEUiIiI9PT0eHh4gIB4hIBkcHBwcHBwcHBydr+JQAAAACHRSTlMABA4YHyQsM5jtaMwAAADfSURBVDjL7ZVBEgMhCAQBAf//42xcNbpAqakcM0ftUmFAAIBE81IqBJdS3lS6zs3bIpB9WED3YYXFPmHRfT8sgyrCP1x8uEUxLMzNWElFOYCV6mHWWwMzdPEKHlhLw7NWJqkHc4uIZphavDzA2JPzUDsBZziNae2S6owH8xPmX8G7zzgKEOPUoYHvGz1TBCxMkd3kwNVbU0gKHkx+iZILf77IofhrY1nYFnB/lQPb79drWOyJVa/DAvg9B/rLB4cC+Nqgdz/TvBbBnr6GBReqn/nRmDgaQEej7WhonozjF+Y2I/fZou/qAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC); display:block; height:44px; margin:0 auto -44px; position:relative; top:-22px; width:44px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p style=&quot; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/p/xsUPb0tLcl/&quot; style=&quot; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;&quot; target=&quot;_top&quot;&gt;A photo posted by Telegram (@telegram_co)&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;time style=&quot; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;&quot; datetime=&quot;2015-01-10T23:48:47+00:00&quot;&gt;Jan 10, 2015 at 3:48pm PST&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;script async defer src=&quot;//platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
This sticker lives on my laptop permanently. I can&amp;#39;t open my Macbook without seeing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn&amp;#39;t stand out much but it&amp;#39;s an important reminder. Laptops are for creating things, not consuming them. (If you want to read a book, or watch Netflix, or catch up on the day&amp;#39;s news, well, that&amp;#39;s what tablets and newspapers and television are for).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#39;Creating&amp;#39; doesn&amp;#39;t have to be entrepreneurial, or even artistic. It&amp;#39;s anything that brings new things into the world, or improves the things that are there. Writing code, editing photographs, finding recipes to cook or learning how to shine your shoes via YouTube. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me it&amp;#39;s a reminder to work on Telegram Co.—both this blog and the &amp;#39;product&amp;#39; side of it. (We&amp;#39;re making &lt;a href=&quot;http://telegram-co.com/&quot;&gt;Japanese denim jeans&lt;/a&gt; in Brooklyn, NY).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it doesn&amp;#39;t have to be entrepreneurial, or even artistic. Writing code, editing photographs, finding recipes to cook or learning how to shine your shoes via YouTube all count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sticker is a reminder to create things every day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 19:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/10/creating-and-consuming.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/10/creating-and-consuming.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Make a Living Doing Art</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What does it take to make a living doing art? There&amp;#39;s this Ira Glass quote:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Nobody tells this to people who are beginners, I wish someone told me. All of us who do creative work, we get into it because we have good taste. But there is this gap. For the first couple years you make stuff, it’s just not that good. It’s trying to be good, it has potential, but it’s not. But your taste, the thing that got you into the game, is still killer. And your taste is why your work disappoints you.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And of course art isn&amp;#39;t just visual art, but anything you make -- if you make music, or write novels, or design clothes or write programs, the sentiment is the same. There&amp;#39;s a sense of &amp;#39;taste&amp;#39; but you have to push past it, to get to what you&amp;#39;re good at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The counterpart to that big quote is Kevin Kelly&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;http://kk.org/thetechnium/2008/03/1000-true-fans/&quot;&gt;1000 true fans&lt;/a&gt;. The idea that with the rise of the Internet, you don&amp;#39;t need a giant audience or a great big megaphone anymore. You just need a small group of people who care about what you&amp;#39;re making. Who care a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; about what you&amp;#39;re making.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is what we&amp;#39;re trying to do with Telegram. We want to make one thing—Japanese denim jeans—and make them very, very well. (Interested? We&amp;#39;re &lt;a href=&quot;http://telegram-co.com&quot;&gt;launching soon&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2015 05:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/06/how-to-make-a-living-doing-art.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/06/how-to-make-a-living-doing-art.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Coffee and Motorcycles</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a coffee-shop a few blocks away from me that sells two things: coffee, and motorcycles. I&amp;#39;m not kidding -- the coffee is strong, the motorcycles are loud, and the patrons love it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s the difference between a cup of coffee and a motorcycle? (How is a raven like a writing desk?). You could say it&amp;#39;s a matter of degree, the idea that both create a sense of speed, energy, and rustic individualism. You could even go further, since with a lot of commodities -- coffee, say, or &lt;a href=&quot;http://telegram-co.com&quot;&gt;denim&lt;/a&gt;, it&amp;#39;s not just about the product, but the story behind it. &amp;quot;A good story will make even the best offer even better,&amp;quot; as the saying goes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And by selling these two things -- a $3 cup of coffee, and a $9000 motorcycle, they seem to make a living.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If only we could all be so cleanly satisfied.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 09:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/02/coffee-and-motorcycles.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2015/01/02/coffee-and-motorcycles.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pen and Paper</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;How good are your tools?&lt;br&gt;
Are they the best, or the most functional?&lt;br&gt;
Are they simple or complex?&lt;br&gt;
Are they expensive or cheap?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of writing or sketching, my requirements are pretty simple:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cahier-style notebooks, either by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/8883704983/?tag=telegramco-20&quot;&gt;Moleskine&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00IQU75AE/?tag=telegramco-20&quot;&gt;Muji&lt;/a&gt;. One advantage of living in New York is that there are three or four Muji stores in Manhattan, each with stacks upon stacks of wonderful Japanese stationery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Black pens. No other color will do. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00DV6EHLS/?tag=telegramco-20&quot;&gt;Le Pen&lt;/a&gt; for felt-tip, or &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/B0000AQNW3/?tag=telegramco-20&quot;&gt;Bic Velocity&lt;/a&gt; for ballpoint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mechanical pencil. Because having to sharpen a pencil is so twentieth-century. I use the simple &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00006IEE4/?tag=telegramco-20&quot;&gt;Sharpwriter&lt;/a&gt;, like you would use in drafting class in grade school.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;White &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/B001Q4HQVU/?tag=telegramco-20&quot;&gt;artist&amp;#39;s erasers&lt;/a&gt;. Because when you erase something, it should be GONE.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s also this weird effect where buying nice notebooks seems to increase the quality and quantity of your ideas (&amp;quot;I have this wonderful notebook, now I should fill it with something&amp;quot;), but if the notebook is TOO nice then you never end up writing in it (&amp;quot;This Moleskine cost $20, hell if I&amp;#39;m putting my amateur scratchings in it&amp;quot;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For &lt;a href=&quot;http://telegram-co.com/&quot;&gt;Telegram&lt;/a&gt; these tools gave me great results. The logo, initial concept, details, and fit were all sketched out with mechanical pencil before being drawn &amp;quot;for real&amp;quot; in Illustrator.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2014 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2014/12/30/pen-and-paper.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2014/12/30/pen-and-paper.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On Writing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If I were to be brutally honest I wouldn&amp;#39;t be writing in the first place. Writing is a hard task: you put down words on paper, and others will read it (if you&amp;#39;re lucky).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reading involves an element of judgment: you agree or disagree with the author, or her style, and you decide on-the-spot whether to keep reading or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the same with making music, or art, or (to the more practical-minded) physical products like clothes or iPhones. You want to create a new thing and it&amp;#39;s difficult, and you&amp;#39;ll catch flak along the way from all angles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the most part it comes as doubt, not judgment. Not &amp;quot;that will never work&amp;quot;, but &amp;quot;Do you think that will work? Aren&amp;#39;t you worried?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Writing is hard. And music is hard, and art is hard, and making products people care about is hard. But we do it anyway. Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because it&amp;#39;s the only work worth doing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2014/12/28/on-writing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2014/12/28/on-writing.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wabi-sabi</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a book I read recently on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/dp/0981484603/?tag=telegramco-20&quot;&gt;Wabi-sabi&lt;/a&gt;. It reflects in itself the philosophy of wabi-sabi: soft cardboard cover, beautifully starched (but imperfect) pages, and a rough-cut edge to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wabi-sabi is the opposite of modernist design. Apple would never allow this kind of imperfection. But it&amp;#39;s a different kind of perfect: the perfect of your grandfather&amp;#39;s pocket-knife, or a motorcycle jacket that&amp;#39;s been ridden across the US and back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The perfect that comes from wear. From the kinds of things that get better with time, and not worse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An iPhone from three years ago is an old iPhone. A motorcycle jacket from three years ago is just getting started.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 16:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://telegram-creative.com/2014/12/21/wabi-sabi.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telegram-creative.com/2014/12/21/wabi-sabi.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
